If you're going to Europe this fall, please don't pack the same wardrobe for Milano, Paris
and London.
Three fashion capitals, but they have three completely different dress codes.
Starting with Paris, here I would pack less and focus on pieces that they work together.
Think of trench or long wool coat, or straight leg denim, ballet flats or pair of loafers.
One good bag that works every day.
Hear me out.
Keep the colors understated.
Think of black, grey, burgundy, navy and cream.
The goal is not to look over styled, it's slightly undone, like I just threw this on
even when you did not.
For Milano, I'm immediately dressing things up.
I would bring tailored trousers, fitness, a beautiful coat or a leather jacket.
Definitely stronger shoes.
Also don't forget here, it's where you can play more with accessories, jewelries, richer
colors like chocolate brown, deep red.
Look, as an Italian, the only thing that I can say is start with your shoes and then
build everything up.
If you're going specifically to Milano, bear in mind it's way more polished and intentional.
London, in my opinion, it's where you experiment, where you literally get your personality out.
But don't forget, we have all the seasons in one day, so definitely bring with you a
coat.
I would personally pack a brown jacket, knitwear, relaxed trousers, definitely your most comfortable
sneakers because you walk a lot.
This is where I would have more fun mixing vintage, checks, leather or something unexpected.
This is only my starter pack.
I will break down exactly what to pack city by city, so tell me, Paris, London or Milan,
which one are you packing for?
That's all for today.
Thank you for listening.